Ta-da! All of this was done in the ocean.
It's amazing.
It feels so good.
MacDonald's.
I wish the Japanese athletes the best of luck!
Yay!
Yoo-hoo!
I'm here in Toyama!
Starting tomorrow? Oh, from today!
The World Table Tennis Tournament has already started.
Yes, I'm here in Toyama!
Look at this! Look at this!
The scenery is so beautiful!
Let's have fun today!
Let's go!
Here we are at X the SKY, Toyama!
Wow, it's all the ocean!
Amazing, isn't it?
Amazing!
98th floor, now coming down.
Starting from the top 2 floors, you can enjoy the view of the 100th floor.
It's so high!
Almost there! It's so high!
It's fun!
Yeah!
Yoo-hoo!
Today is the third day!
Yesterday was my first reporting job since the World Table Tennis Tournament started, and I was so nervous.
But with the help of everyone, the staff and many other people
I finished the first day without any problems.
I have some free time now.
I think I'll do some shopping.
I was thinking of buying souvenirs for the members.
I went shopping.
It's like a Korean pharmacy.
I bought some things that Shio-chan asked me to buy
I bought some packs that I was going to give to everyone.
I'm going to go to Olim Young's one more time.
One more place
It's the second day of the World Table Tennis Championships!
We've just finished the men's game.
Next, I'm going to go to the women's game.
This is my first time to report on a sporting event.
I'm learning a lot every day, and I'm doing my best.
I'm off! Fighting!
Well, that's it for the second day of the World Table Tennis Championships!
Men's and Women's live coverage is over!
I have been studying every day!
Today, too, I was able to learn a lot of things while watching the live broadcast!
Here are some goods! So cute!
I'm going to sleep well today, study hard, and head out in the morning!
I'm going to work hard on the live broadcast tomorrow too!
Cheese tapparrub!
Sukimchi
Daikon radish
Kimchi that tastes like wee-wee
Rice
I took one more bite of rice!
I'm taking a picture of the opposite side of the picture
Art rice
Thank you for the meal!
Thank you for watching!
Good afternoon.
Today marks the fourth day of the World Table Tennis Championships!
It's over.
The fourth day is.
Yes, the women's and men's live broadcast is over.
Kumi-chan is here!
Wow!
Today is the end for me
I'd like to pass the baton to Kumi.
I would like to pass the baton to Kumi.
I hope you will do your best from now on.
I hope you will do your best.
I will do my best.
I will do my best to follow your advice!
Yay!
Hello.
I'm here in Korea.
I'm here today.
I don't have a match for Japanese players.
I have a little bit
I have a recording.
Other than that, I have time.
I'm going to take the train now
I'm going to a place called
I heard there's a place called Somyung Theatre.
I've heard that there's a grocery store and a café there.
I'd like to go there.
It's so cute!
This one?
Let's go there.
It's a blowfish restaurant.
Fugu nabe?
I'll enjoy it.
Thank you very much.
It smells so good!
Fugu nabe!
I think this is my first time to eat puffer fish!
It's a real blowfish!
A real blowfish!
Pufferfish
This is a blowfish bun.
Manjuu
Looks delicious
the one that says "Delicious!
From today
I'll be broadcasting the World Table Tennis Tournament.
I'll be watching live from the World Table Tennis Championships.
I was just...
I've been watching Bee Pan.
I'm getting more and more nervous.
In my own way
I'm trying to convey to the Japanese people
I will do my best
I will do my best.
Now
Well, both men's and women's teams have just finished the second round of the final tournament
Both men's and women's teams have just finished the second round of the final tournament.
Both men's and women's teams have won and will participate in the Paris Olympics!
Congratulations!
For me, it was my first report today.
I was very nervous.
Reporting in the atmosphere of the games
It's not often that I'm reporting from behind the games.
I felt nervous.
I could see some issues that I need to work on.
Tomorrow is my last day.
I will do my best to make the most of tomorrow.
I'm at station number 3.
Get off the train.
I went up to the subway and headed straight for the ocean.
No one goes to the beach on such a cold day.
Maybe it's empty.
It's cold.
Wow, it's beautiful.
Then I'll dance here for a bit.
So, here we are at the ocean of 30,000 li.
Ta-da!
Mamacchan has come to Toyama!
Here she comes!
I watched the game today, how was it?
I've been watching the game since you started.
I also saw Kumi on TV yesterday.
I was really excited even through the TV.
But seeing it live was totally different.
But seeing it live was a totally different experience, combined with the excitement of the venue.
I was also moved by the actual live commentary.
I was very moved.
Everyone is really giving it their all.
It's been a really hot battle, hasn't it?
I'll do my best to finish it off properly.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
I came here for lunch on the second day!
Next, we had bibimbap!
Here is the bibimbap in a stone pot!
Amazing!
A commemorative photo!
Tempura tsukusan!
Crispy!
Delicious!
Good night
Good night.
A little thin? A little.
It's definitely a little Banks-ish.
It's got a lot of ingredients. It's a quick bite.
Delicious.
The dough is not too thick.
Okay, so we're done.
It looked so delicious!
Thank you very much.
Now that I'm full.
I'm going to work hard all at once!
We found a big dinosaur!
After we ate, we were thinking of going home.
It's amazing!
If it were you, you'd recognize it right away, wouldn't you?
I wonder if it's a Flachiosaurus or something.
Oh, it says here...
It's not a stegosaurus at all.
But it's the type you often hear about.
A stegosaurus.
Amazing!
Carrier is here, too.
I can't see the carrier's face.
I can't see the carrier's face. - I can't see the carrier's face.
I can't see the carriers' faces.
I can't see the carriers' faces
Sounds fun.
Want to give it a try?
I'd like to try it.
I just found the slide.
I didn't know there was such a place
I didn't know there was such a place to have fun.
I didn't know there was a place to have fun
Oh, my God.
It's great!
It's so loud!
Yoo-hoo!
That's great.
That's great!
Here we go
Japanese athletes
I wish them good results
Amazing!
That's great.
Huh...
I've digested it.
I just left the venue after the semi-finals.
Wow, it was really wonderful.
First of all, Zhang won the game in reverse.
He won 2 games, and then he had to win 3 more games to win.
Then he won 3 games in a row to win the match.
I can't believe she is 15 years old, and I can't believe she is a junior high school student,
Also, as Hina Hayata said, I couldn't believe she was a human being.
I was so encouraged by her, and even though she is younger than me, I thought she was really wonderful.
It gave me the courage to do my best, too.
Hina Hayata and Miyu Hirano both won in straight sets,
Tomorrow, we will finally play China.
They are already known as a strong competitor,
But after watching today's match, my expectations for them to win increased,
I will be there cheering for the Japanese as much as I can and hope for a good performance from Japan.
For lunch on the third day, we went to a spicy octopus hot pot restaurant called "Nachpokkum.
It looks delicious.
The ending of "Hajime Shacho".
Hmmm...
Well, well, well... I'm full. I'm ready to go.
We're going to the women's final now, so I'm going to do my best.
This is the official character of the World Table Tennis Team Tournament.
I thought it was a penguin, but it seems to be a seagull. I heard there are seagulls flying in the sea in Busan.
I was told yesterday that they are seagulls.
It's Choppy.
Choppy Choppy Choppy Choppy Choppy
Choppy luppies. Choppy luppies. Coppy luppies.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm going to go back to the hotel, change my clothes, and go to the venue again.
The live broadcast of the women's team final of the World Table Tennis Championships has just finished!
I really appreciate your hard work, although I was able to participate in the live broadcast for two days.
I was able to participate in the live broadcast for two days, but it all happened so fast.
I felt the excitement from the audience and I was really glad that I could be there to cheer for the girls.
I was really happy to be able to cheer for the women's team this time, and although we lost 3-2 to the Chinese players, it was a really great match.
I was able to see a really great match.
I will continue to support table tennis in the future. I love table tennis.
I love ping-pong and I'm going to continue to support ping-pong from now on.
Thank you very much for your hard work. I'm going back home tomorrow, so I'm going to enjoy sightseeing again.
I'm going back tomorrow, so I'd like to go back to the city and enjoy some sightseeing.
Traditional market in Pingyun
I want to see something cute and buy a hat!
I want to see something!
It looks Korean!
It's a strange shape.
Strange? What do you think? Do you guys think I'm weird?
What? You see it? The side.
Not really.
Which way?
It's kind of funny.
A little funny?
I'll take this one.
I'll take this one then.
I got it.
I got the new one right behind the cash register.
I ordered tteokbokki.
It's amazing!
A beaker or something like that!
The soup was shaped like something you don't see in Japan!
What is this?
It looks like deep-fried tofu!
Like fried tofu?
I'd like to try some.
Bon appétit!
I got it!
Delicious!
Spicy
Spicy but sweet and hot
Delicious
Comes later
What do you want me to say after that?
Hmm?
It's not fried tofu.
It's good.
It's spicy, so it's perfect with this soup.
Spicy.
Spicy, but delicious!
It's kind of warming my cheeks, too.
The newest Coop.
I'm going to buy a hot dog now.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Wow! Thank you so much.
Looks delicious.
I just bought some hot chocolate!
Bon appétit!
I think I'll just leave it like this.
It's hot.
Yeah, it's still dough
Actuality.
Delicious! Mochi Mochi
Like fried bread
like fried bread
Sweet part is here.
I think it's expensive.
There's a heart here
Heart.
Oh, no.
It's gonna get erased.
I can only write as far as Hina.
I want to write "Hinata".
I want to write "Hinata Saka Channel" if I have to...
Couple.
Wait a minute.
I'm going home.
We're not going home.
What's going on? Is it gone?
It's gone!
What? It's gone!
I was about to put the shovel back and take a picture.
It's gone!
I didn't see anyone.
I wanted to take a picture of it disappearing.
So fast!
The ocean is a fleeting thing, isn't it?
That's life, isn't it?
Maybe I'll take a picture of the ocean.
Wow!
Nice.
Thanks.